rssportscars.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy - RSsportscars.com

At RSsportscars.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit RSsportscars.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. At that time, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address.

You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To send periodic emails

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.rssportscars.com/site/terms-of-use.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [info@rssportscars.com](mailto:info@rssportscars.com) or through the contact form.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

 _Initial version effective July 12, 2013  
Last modified on March 18, 2014._
